When I woke up this morning,
I found myself smack in the middle
of another weird-ass situation.
Oh, for crying out loud, another one?
These freaky creature things are coming out of the woods.
Good work!
I can hear my heart, and how do you think you know?
The heart of the moon will be.
The beginning was that time.
You were suddenly suddenly in the eye.
The moment you appeared before you came out.
You were the one who was chosen.
You were the one who was chosen!
You were a man who was chosen.
Thank you.
Good morning, everybody.
Looks like it's going to be another hot one in Fukuoka today.
We're going to have to break out the parasols, fans, water bottles, hate, whatever you've got.
Hey, Icarus.
Yes, Master?
Who the hell is that?
Is she from your world?
She's got wings like you.
I'm not sure.
Well, she certainly looks like you.
I mean, not just the wings, the collar, the weird ear thingies.
You do not get to make my home into your new clubhouse for freaky angel girls.
Is this sinking in?
Hey, Mr. Littlebug.
I hope I didn't hear what I thought I just heard.
I'm sorry.
What was that you called me there?
I called you Mr. Littlebug.
Who else in the room would I be calling Mr.?
Right.
Thanks.
Icarus, you know my motto?
Peace and quiet is the only way to live?
I'm having a hell of a time maintaining that with just you here.
See what I'm getting at?
Yes, Master.
Hey, move your ass and get this chick out of here!
Enough's enough already!
Let me get back to my peace and quiet!
Everyone always seems to have such a good time at Tomoki.
Who's in there?
Why do we have to bring her along again?
Who cares?
The more the merrier.
At least that's always been my philosophy.
I don't think that's true in this case.
Originally, Tomo and I were supposed to go to the beach by ourselves today.
See how well that worked out.
Yes!
A winner!
Top prize is a day trip for two to the beach!
You kids have a great time!
Yeah!
Here you go.
Congratulations.
I did it!
I won!
You realize the two of us haven't been on a trip together since we were kids?
You played enough.
You were bound to win something.
Oh, I cannot wait!
And I'm so happy the rest of the gang won't be joining.
Congratulations!
I'm so excited for you.
You both won a day trip for two to the beach.
I can't believe it!
What a great day!
Really!
Sorry, Sahara.
Why?
What are you sorry for?
Because I know that you were supposed to be going on this trip just you and Tomoko.
No!
Forget it!
I'm cool with the way things turned out.
Guess I can't stay disappointed forever.
I mean, hey, it's still a day at the beach.
So do you have a name or do we have to give you one?
It's Nymph.
Okay, weird, but Nymph it is, I suppose.
Oh, yeah, I almost forgot.
I made breakfast rice balls for all of us.
Here you go.
Take your pick.
Oh, this one.
Why has another Angeloid appeared here seemingly out of the blue?
That's what I said.
They're coming out of the freaking woodwork.
Wow!
Your wings glow rainbow colors all over.
They're just beautiful.
You seem a lot different from Icarus, that's for sure.
Of course I seem different.
I'm not an alpha type.
So what are you?
I guess you'd call me the generation after alpha, if generation's the right word.
With you side by side like that, you could pass for sisters.
One of them, two of them, it's all the same.
Just keep an eye on them.
It's not the same at all.
I just want my peace and quiet back.
Whoa.
Boobies!
Boobie time!
Better be careful, Tomoki.
Come on.
Where did you all get those swimsuits?
Prez felt bad for the girls, so she bought them.
Icarus, what happened to your back?
I don't see your wings.
Correct.
I am able to withdraw my wings whenever I need to.
But they are still here.
This is as small as they get.
I can actually make my wings invisible.
Oh.
That sounds pretty useful.
I asked them to prop us up an umbrella over there.
What say we all go enjoy ourselves?
This is going to be awesome!
Nymph kind of bugs the crap out of me.
Hey, Eve.
We're never going to make it unless you pick up the pace.
Mizuki, you're never going to find happiness, Eve.
Oh, screw her.
I'm at the beach, and I am going to have me some fun.
Service.
Set!
It's just like I dreamed it.
Beach volleyball is a beautiful sport.
The way Sohara's chest heaves and bounces.
Best day ever!
Tomoki, quit staring at my chest!
He must be getting to you.
You're imagining things.
Jerk.
Nice bike.
Way to go, Nymph.
Nice bike, my ass.
Why did you put so much power behind it?
You trying to kill me or something?
It's your own stupid fault for zoning out.
Hmm.
I'm not responsible.
Master, are you all right?
What is her problem?
Okay, beach volleyball is bullshit.
Well, then what do you say we take a boat out on the water?
Yeah, sure.
That might be fun.
Huh.
It's crunch time, ladies and gents.
We're coming down to the water.
Sugata!
Check this out, folks.
We've got our...
Come on, Sugata.
You still have a long way to go.
Oh, that's not good.
I think we should just let him do his thing.
Yeah.
I'm going to go find the boat rental place and grab us one, okay?
Hey, nymph.
Hot dog?
And now you say thank you.
Go ahead, give it a try.
Come on, it won't take too much effort.
You're not the boss of me, little bug.
Jeez, I'm sorry.
This is great.
You're kind of cute when you actually smile, you know that?
Don't sit next to me.
Hey, chill out.
Hey, I've been meaning to ask you, why did you come here anyway?
Why?
No real reason, I guess.
I just wanted to find out for myself what the lower world was like.
Ah, or maybe it was something like you were worried about how Icarus was doing and you
came here to check up on her.
You two are friends, right?
Yeah, something like that, I suppose.
Because I sure didn't come all the way down here to make friends with you.
Oh, I see.
Thanks.
Oh, yeah.
Where did Icarus go anyway?
She's out there.
See, I told you so.
What is that lunatic doing at the bottom of the ocean?
Do you require assistance, Master?
You don't need to worry.
Diving down to that depth is a cinch for an alpha like her.
It's all part of their design capabilities.
At least try to float around like a normal person.
I mean, what if someone saw you down there?
But my wings absorb water, so no matter what, I end up sinking to the bottom.
I can't do anything about it.
You're so dumb sometimes.
Have you ever thought about looking at me as an example and just not getting water on your wings?
Well, they're already wet now.
Oh, crap.
No way I can leave Icarus to her own devices.
Guess I'll teach her to swim.
Tomoki, I rented the boat.
Check it out.
Hey, Tomoki.
No, you're doing it wrong.
Your legs go straight out for the flutter kick.
I'll keep pulling.
You keep kicking.
I'll try, Master.
Is this right?
Sorry, still wrong.
Kick harder.
Tomo, what about us?
He can be such a jerk.
After I went through the trouble of renting this stupid boat.
I don't care anymore.
But if I could swim, this would suck a little less.
Hold up.
You're serious?
You never learned how to swim?
No.
Here, then I'll pull you through the water.
It'll be fun.
Come on, give it a shot.
Your legs go straight out for the flutter kick.
Tomoki, I'm scared.
You're fine.
I got you, and I won't let you go, okay?
I wonder if he's forgotten about that time.
Oh, no.
What happened?
When did I drift out this far?
And great, I let the ore go.
I've been carried away.
I...
I gotta get back.
Cool.
Let's take another.
It got kind of cloudy all of a sudden.
Hey, has anybody seen Suhara?
Now that you mention it,
I saw her hop into a boat by herself not long ago.
Maybe she's paddling around.
Yeah.
That's right.
I forgot, I told her I'd go boating with her.
Hang on.
Is that her?
Suhara, wait!
Suhara!
Oh, no!
Amazing.
They're flying.
In your lane.
Can't do anything on your own.
Suhara!
I can't get to the surface.
Here, I got you!
Are you okay?
Tomaki...
And Nymph, too?
Thank you both.
No, I owe you an apology, Suhara.
I thought if Icarus caused a scene,
it'd end up biting me in the ass like it always does.
I guess I just focused on that and forgot all about you.
I really am very sorry.
No more going out on the water by yourself, understand?
It's dangerous for anybody, let alone someone who never learned to swim.
I can't believe it.
He actually remembered.
Right.
The drama's over.
Let's get this party swinging again.
Oh, wait.
The sun's going down.
I'm sorry, Suhara.
Don't worry.
It's okay.
Thanks for saving me, Tomaki.
Hold on a second, Bug.
Huh?
Why are you trying to act all smooth?
The only reason you were able to save her was because you had my help.
Duh.
I'm not stupid.
I know.
And I haven't even gotten a thank you yet.
Oh, sorry.
I guess thanks, Nymph.
You help me out a lot.
Can't say I'm really feeling it over here, Bug.
What?
You've got a lot of nerve for a freaking insect.
Icarus?
What's the deal with your loudmouth friend?
Why does she keep calling me a bug?
It's about time to start packing our things up to go home.
You know, I couldn't agree more.
Oh, yeah.
Icarus, before we leave, I want you and I to go over what you've learned one more time.
All right, Master.
Like I said, dummy, the flutter kick's all in the legs.
We're staying.
Huh?
It's not fair to me that you've only spent time with Icarus since we've gotten here!
So I don't want to go home!
So we're going to stay here and we're going to do whatever I want on the beach tomorrow!
You crazy person!
A pass for a Seaside Lodge?
Your angel.
How is she?
All right, yeah.
The thing about that is, another one showed up.
She's not bad, but whatever.
Be careful.
What are you doing here?
Yes.
Yes isn't an answer!
No.
You're supposed to be in Sahara's room, so get back in there and go to sleep before you make us both look insane!
Pardon, Master?
What is it?
I was hoping you could explain to me what it is like to sleep.
Huh.
As angeloids, we were not designed with any kind of sleep functions in our programming.
That is why I don't understand what it means to sleep or to have dreams.
Okay, so what the heck have you been doing every night while I've been going to sleep?
I simply sat by your side, waiting for you. Waiting patiently for you to wake up.
All right, guess I'm awake now.
You want to walk down to the beach?
Master...
You must have been cramped keeping your wings under wraps all day.
There shouldn't be anyone down there this time of night.
You can stretch those suckers out as much as you want.
Thank you.
Icarus' specs detail that she can drop to a maximum depth of 3,000 meters and she can operate continuously without oxygen for 720 hours.
I'd estimate Nymph has roughly the same capabilities.
What's the purpose of sending another angeloid down here now?
This is all so strange.
I think it must be hella nice not needing to sleep.
But for some reason, I don't know why, I felt bad for Icarus when I heard that.
I wonder if that other angel sits up awake all night, unable to sleep too.
Master?
Master, it's about time for us to head back.
All right.
Let go of me, you stupid little bug!
And here we are being the nicest guys in the world to you, too!
Nymph!
Sorry.
She has kind of a big mouth on her sometimes.
Come on, let's go.
Hold it.
We're not done talking to your friend yet.
We just got concerned because she's so young and she was strolling around the beach alone.
Let me go!
And stay away from me, you big stinky bug!
What'd you say?
Hey, maybe your buddy can explain.
How are we bugs?
Huh?
Just what do you think you are doing to my master?
You got wings?
Hmm.
Alpha.
I ask what you are doing to him, and I expect you to give me a satisfactory answer.
What is going on?
Stop it!
What the holy hell was that?
You shouldn't be doing stuff like that, ever!
We're going.
Two angels.
Icarus I've been wondering yes master that watermelon you've been holding like a newborn
baby is probably like completely rotten in sight by now what do you plan to do with it
oh man that just makes you look even cuter sorry I got mad at you last night I swear it's just
you look like some killer Android weapon like you'd seen a movie or something
I guess it caught me off guard and I kind of freaked out
yeah
I never knew her love
love me
if you love me
the
news
I
am
It's not love, it's not love
It's not love
I wonder if Icarus got rusty from being out in the ocean
Cause I keep hearing this weird sound
Here, why don't you try eating this?
Master, here is your tea
She seems a whole lot better now
Next time, the brainy heart-pounding transfer students